hello everybody this is my version of
the digital campfire I'd like to share
with you some songs I wrote in the past
year or so
this one's called Cain and Abel and all
the songs that I'll be sharing with you
in this digital campfire are based on
the book of Genesis and I don't mean
them to be religious particularly I'm
mostly interested in the depth and of
these stories and how well they work
with the folk blues genre so here I go
Cain and Abel
[Music]
one sided brother my father's favorite
Sloan
the sacrifice was burning
[Music]
[Applause]
I was the awkward one
[Music]
and beyond it burning and the other
cream
[Music]
my brother Shawn
wanted all my dreams
[Music]
we shivered in the animals I come in
earth
[Music]
sit crashed at my door
accursed my very hurt
cat howling hurry Tamar just like stone
[Music]
man
sure
[Music]
my brother mine
and shame
[Music]
the earth darkened with blood
my brother
[Music]
trade my father's love
he's selling his subconscious
[Music]
Christ amen machines terrible news
Scot scaring birds grow any
[Music]
water in the slits
falling on the star
mark upon us
[Music]
now Elijah for me the weapons are
on the warring earth
[Music]
now the truth in love melt the art
weapons of the beast to keep us down to
me
[Music]
calling
my brother's keeper I call
[Music]
I want
Oh
when
[Music]
[Applause]